# DO ANH DUY

### FULL STACK DEVELOPER



7/213 TanMai Street, Hanoi City 🗣

anhduycnttx1@gmail.com

https://github.com/duyda1402

+84 962819197



# SUMMARY

I am software developer with almost 3 years of experience designing and delivering technological solutions. Proficient in Typescript, Nodejs, Python... specialize in the development of financial applications, including those related to banking and electronic wallets. Furthermore, I have a history of developing applications in blockchain technology, have comprehension of decentralized technologies.

# **EXPERIENCES**

#### Feb 2023 - Present

### Mid-Level Full Stack at Synodus

Use: Nodejs, Nestjs, Reactjs, ...

- Develop a system to manage client accounts, concierge services, chat ports, customer support, and more.
- Build an application for managing crypto accounts and facilitating the depositing, withdrawing, and transferring of crypto currencies.
- Interact with the blockchain, executing multisignature transaction signatures and more.

### Otc 2022 - Feb 2023

### **Junior Full Stack at Nuclent**

Use: Nestjs, Reactjs ....

- Develop a Landingpage for customer loan account creation with partners Vietinbank and GRAB.
- Develop an Admin page for loan management with an integrated automated approval process and implement a multi-level loan approval.

### Nov 2021 - May 2022

#### Fresher Front-End at MobiFone

Use: Reactjs, React-Native, ...

• Develop and implement payment intermediary services, encompassing e-wallets, mobile money, Fintech, and other related technologies.

# **EDUCATION**

#### University

2015 - 2021 | Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Computer engineering majors

## SKILL

#### Languages

Typescript Skillful

Python Experienced

Go Experienced

#### **Frameworks**

ReactJSSkillfulNestjs - NodejsSkillfulReact-NativeSkillfulWeb3Experienced

#### **Databases**

PostgreSQLSkillfulMongoDBSkillful

#### **UI Libraries**

Antd Skillful

Mantine Skillful

Tailwind Skillful

# LANGUAGES

Vietnamese native language
English reading, writing